Hi guys, my name is Dmitri.
I'm an artist, designer, developer...
...and the creator of Analog.Cafe:
"The REMARKABLE Photo Blog."
So, what is Analog.Cafe?
...and why is it REMARKABLE?
Well, to put it simply it is a curated community blog...
...that lets anyone who's into FILM PHOTOGRAPHY...
...to effortlessly contribute and collaborate.
What I'm trying to do here is to create a PUBLICATION that makes...
...working together a natural process.
Even for introverts.
Let's say Cara submits a photograph of a train in Sri Lanka.
And it gets featured on Analog.Cafe.
A lot of people get to enjoy her work.
Now, imagine Finn,
who is working on a photo essay about trains around the world.
He can use Cara's image from the "Features" library...
...to supplement his photographs.
Finn gets to extend his vision.
Cara gets full credit.
Automatically.
So, here's how it's going to work:
I've already coded and designed the interface...
...of the website.
The same design is going to be used for the Zine - your reward.
A physical extension of Analog.Cafe.
A lot of the technical details concerning making the website...
...are being worked on right now.
Your contribution will help me pay...
...for talented developers...
...to connect the interface of the website...
...to a database.
It will be a beautiful, beautiful blog!